ncl.com 2014-11-04

# Privacy Policy

#### LAST UPDATED: March 6, 2008

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") applies to information received by NCL Corporation Ltd., its subsidiaries and affiliates (the "Company"). This notice describes our privacy policy ("Policy") with respect to data collected via www.ncl.com and [www.ncl.co.uk](http://www.ncl.co.uk/) (together, the "Website") and elsewhere.

This Policy explains what information we collect about you and what we do with it. The Company reserves the right to revise this privacy policy at any time. We will notify you of any material changes to the Policy by posting the new Policy here and by changing the "Effective Date" at the top. You should periodically read this Policy to learn of any revisions.

### What information do we collect?

When you take a cruise with us, ask for information about the Company, visit the Website or through various other methods, we collect information about you and your visit. We collect credit card information from you where applicable, in order to facilitate your purchases. We collect individually-identifiable personal information ("Personal Data") that you provide to us such as your name, e-mail address, street address and telephone number. You supply us this Personal Data when you take an action such as taking a cruise, requesting information, purchasing something and/or some other action to voluntarily supply your Personal Data to us.

On our Website, in addition to Personal Data, we also collect non-personally identifiable information that allows us to track the number of visitors we receive and the way they navigate through the Website. This non-personally identifiable data includes information about the web site the visitor arrived from and departs to as well as the IP address of the computer being used to access our Website. While it may be possible to correlate this information to particular individuals, we do not generally do so, and we limit our use of this information to its aggregate form reflecting all visitors to the Website. We may share this aggregated information with other third parties.

### What do we do with the information we collect?

We use the Personal Data we collect to provide our services and engage in advertising and marketing activities. We use credit card and/or other financial information that you provide us to fulfill your order or request. The Company takes reasonable precautions in order to ensure the safety and security of our customer’s online transactions. Credit card numbers that you enter on our billing webpage are encrypted and transmitted through SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) technology. SSL is the industry standard for securing Web-messaging transactions.

On our Website, we use IP addresses and anonymous demographic information in the aggregate to share with advertisers and market researchers, and to improve the design of our Website so as to better serve our customers. We do not drill down into anonymous demographic information in order to analyze and/or collect personal information from these sources. However, we reserve the right to do so in order to investigate unlawful conduct and/or breaches of this Policy.

### Do we share the information we collect with third parties?

We share Personal Data with our business partners to provide our services, for market and industry research purposes, for advertising and marketing purposes, and for other reasons. If you prefer, you can choose that your information not be shared with our business partners or used for marketing purposes by contacting us at the address listed below.

The Company may transfer any information in its databases, including but not limited to Personal Data, to an affiliate or third party as part of a transfer of business assets.

The Company may also release Personal Data in special cases in order to comply with any requests from law enforcement and government agencies, to enforce the Website Terms of Use and other agreements, and to protect customers and others. We may do so when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or advisable, including, for instance, to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with the rights or property of the Company, another user or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

The Company may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the Website or the Company’s rights or property.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are pieces of information generated by web servers and stored in your computer for future access. We use them to study visitors' use of the Website and to improve your navigation of it. For example, a cookie can allow you to continue shopping without having to re-enter items already placed in the shopping cart. The majority of Web browsers accept cookies, but the "help" menu on your browser should give you options for preventing, accepting, or receiving notice of new cookies. You can configure your web-browser to disable cookies, but doing so may impair your use of the Website.

### What about Third Party Links?

This Website may have hyperlinks to other websites. The Company is not responsible for their privacy practices or content. We urge you to review the privacy policy of any website that you visit.

### Security

While the Company strives to protect Personal Data and user privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. This Privacy Policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond the Company's control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, the Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we use reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

### Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on the Website are delivered to you by our advertising partners. Our advertising partners may use cookies. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. The Company does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed on the computer of any uses by the third-party ad servers or ad networks.

### Children

The Website is not intended for children under the age of 13, and the Company does not intentionally collect Personal Data from children under 13. If you have reason to believe that we have collected Personal Data from someone under 13 years of age, please let us know.

### How do I opt-out or unsubscribe?

All e-mails you receive from us will include specific instructions on how to unsubscribe and you may unsubscribe at any time.

(1) Follow the instructions provided in any Company e-mail;

(2) [Click here.](http://ebm.email.ncl.com/r/regf2?a=0&aid=2076736576&n=1)

(3) Send mail to the following address:

Norwegian Cruise Line  
Internet Development Department  
7665 Corporate Center Drive  
Miami, Florida 33126  
(305) 436-4000  

Please allow up to 2 weeks to be unsubscribed from all NCL emails.

### Claims

If you believe that the Company has acted inconsistently with this Policy, please notify us either at the address above at [_webmaster@ncl.com_](mailto:webmaster@ncl.com) and we will try to resolve your concern.
